atlanticcitynj.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

The [www.atlanticcitynj.com](http://www.atlanticcitynj.com/) website is owned and operated by the New Jersey Casino Reinvestment Development Authority (collectively referred to herein as "the CRDA," "us" or "we"). The CRDA is a non-profit entity created to identify and market the diverse recreational, entertainment, cultural and historical attractions in Atlantic City and it's surrounding region.The CRDA is dedicated to serving your needs. We care about your privacy and have implemented a privacy policy that clearly outlines the policies and terms of use applicable to this site and your use thereof.

#### Information We Collect

There are three types of information that can be collected on this web site - usage information, non-personal information and personal information.

  * **Usage Information** \- Our web server automatically recognizes and saves the domain name and IP address through which you arrived on the web site. Other aggregate, site information we may collect includes information like entry page, time on site and number of page views. This data is used for internal review of traffic patterns to and on our site and can help us to improve our users'; experience. None of this information is personally identifiable and will only be used to find out how site visitors use our services and the site.
  * **Non-Personally Identifiable Information** \- We may also request non-personally identifiable information, such as annual income range, buying preferences,  your location, education and age range, also known as demographic and profile data but this information is optional. This data helps us to determine the interests of our site visitors and lets us tailor site content, events and news, accordingly. Aggregate and anonymous information may be shared with our member organizations but the CRDA does not sell this information to third parties.
  * **Personal Information** – (name, address, email address, phone number) If you request information from the CRDA by filling out a form on the site, we may need your e-mail address, street address or phone number in order to respond. This information is added to the CRDA database, but its use is limited to updating your Non-PII information and responding to your requests. 

The CRDA does not collect or store any personal information that you do not expressly provide, nor will it send you any additional emails past satisfying your request unless you expressly agree to receive these emails. This is called "opting in." If you opt in, you will receive occasional emails from the CRDA notifying you of events, concerts and regional or travel news of interest. You may unsubscribe at any time.

#### A Special Note about Children

This website is directed to adults, not children. While the CRDA does not encourage children to use the site, it takes its responsibility to protect children's privacy seriously. In compliance with the Children's Privacy Protection Act, the CRDA does not, knowingly, collect personal information from children under 13.

If information is provided by a child without his or her parents' permission and the CRDA unwittingly collects it, the CRDA will provide parents with a description of the specific types of personal information collected from the child, the opportunity at any time to refuse to permit the CRDA further use or maintenance of the child's personal information and a means that is reasonable for the parent to obtain any personal information collected from that child. 

#### Cookies

We use cookies on this web site. A cookie is a text file placed on your computer or mobile device by some web pages that you visit. When you visit the site again, the web server retrieves the cookie and reconfigures itself based on your profile and preferences, such as previous pages you visited and any information you provide via a form.

Cookies are generated by web sites such as atlanticcitynj.com provide users with a personalized and an enhanced online experience. By assigning and storing a unique user name cookie on your computer or mobile device, we are able to offer you personalized collection, filtering, and delivery of information including serving advertisements to you while you are visiting Atlantic City that we feel will be of the greatest interest and value to you. Also, overall, aggregated usage information derived from cookies helps us improve our offerings by showing us how different areas of the web site are being used. We also utilize cookies that record your general location based on your IP address and your interactions with our media to monitor how effective our media is at inspiring you to visit Atlantic City. Cookies, by themselves, cannot be used to reveal or discover the identity of the individual user. Your acceptance of our cookie will not compromise your anonymity while using our web site. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but you can control cookies through your browser preference settings. If you choose to reject cookies, certain functions and applications on the site may be disallowed as a result, and you will not benefit from any personalized and enhanced services that are available. If you wish to opt out of cookies that allow us to serve Atlantic City advertisements while you are in Atlantic City and collect aggregate information on arrivals, click [here](mailto:dc.arrivalist.com/optout/). 

#### Contests & Sweepstakes

On occasion, the CRDA will conduct online contests, giveaways, or sweepstakes, which require information to be provided for eligibility. The information collected in these contests is subject to our Privacy Policy and conditions of use and is not shared. If the user does not provide the requested information he/she may not be eligible for the contest. Depending on the structure of the promotion, the submitted information is entered into a random drawing of the names to determine the winner. At the time a user enters a contest, giveaway or sweepstakes on atlanticcitynj.com, he or she may choose to receive continued e-mails from the CRDA (called opting in). If the entrant does not choose to receive e-mails (called opting out), the information submitted by the entrant is inactivated in the database after the contest has ended. 

#### This website uses Google AdWords

This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Atlantic City website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.

#### Links to Third Party Web Sites

There are a few sections on the CRDA web site that are hosted by various partners of the CRDA. Some of these partners maintain the look and feel of our web site or a segment of our web site, and sometimes it may not be evident when a user is on one of these sections. These pages are governed by the partner's privacy policy and terms and conditions of use. 

#### Electronic Newsletters

We offer free, electronic newsletters, updates and e-mail reminders as a service to our registrants, based upon your voluntary subscription. You will only receive an electronic newsletter if you have requested it (opted-in). We do not allow third parties, including advertisers or partners to send email to our list. 

#### Opt-out for Convention Trade:

All convention, event, meeting and tour clients have the option to opt out of all information from the CRDA.  
Conference meeting leads are distributed at the client’s direction to include, if preferred, instruction that all responses be directed to the CRDA to avoid direct solicitation from each respective property.

Additionally all convention, meeting, trade and tour events have the option to opt out of being on any public calendar of events managed through the CRDA and Atlantic City Convention Center. 

#### Opt-out for Travel Trade:

The Tourism Department gives the travel trade the option to opt out of any or all communication within our membership. Any requests that come in to the Tourism Department from the Travel Trade will be directed to all members of the CRDA who fit the criteria of the travel trades’ request. At any time the requestor may ask that a request not be sent to a certain member or members via written communication. 

#### Disclaimer and Release With Respect to Any Linked Site or Other Third Party

Any transaction that you enter into with any linked site or other third party via or as a result of viewing our web site is solely between you and such linked site or other third party. By using this web site, you understand and agree that the CRDA has no responsibility for any other sites or third party content or transactions. You further agree that you will hold the CRDA harmless and not liable, and release the CRDA from any all suits and/or claims, should you have any dispute over or problem with any such sites, site content or transactions. 

#### General Legal Notice and Disclaimer

References herein to any product or service offered by a linked site or other third party do not constitute or imply endorsement or recommendation by the CRDA. While the CRDA makes every effort to present accurate and reliable information on this web site, the CRDA does not approve or certify such information nor does it guarantee the accuracy, completeness, efficacy, timeliness or correct sequencing of such information.

Use of such information is voluntary and reliance on it should only be undertaken after an independent review of its applicability, accuracy, completeness, efficacy and timeliness with regard to the user's specific needs and purposes. the CRDA (including its employees and agents) is not responsible for and expressly disclaims all liability for, damages of any kind arising out of use, reference to, or reliance on the information available through this web site. No approvals, recommendations, endorsements, guarantees or warranties, including, but not limited to, any express or implied warranties of merchantability or fitness for any particular use or purpose of products or services named on this Internet site are made by the CRDA. 

#### Terms of Use

By visiting, using and/or submitting information to this web site, you agree to the terms and conditions contained in this Privacy Policy and conditions of use and/or any other agreement that we might have with you. If you do not agree to any of these terms and conditions you should not use this web site or any products or services offered by the CRDA, a linked site, or other third party discussed herein.

You agree that any dispute over privacy or the terms contained in this Privacy Policy and conditions of use, or any other agreement we have with you, will be governed by the laws of the State of New Jersey. You also agree to arbitrate such disputes in New Jersey and to abide by any limitation on damages contained in any agreement that may be reached with you. 

#### Notices and Changes to Our Privacy Policy

As our services change from time to time, this Privacy Policy and conditions of use are expected to change. We reserve the right to amend the Privacy Policy and conditions of use at any time, for any reason, without notice to you, other than the posting of the amended Privacy Policy and conditions of use at this site.

It is your responsibility to check our site frequently to see the current Privacy Policy and conditions of use that are in effect and any changes that may have been made to them. The use of your information is subject to the Privacy Policy and conditions of use in effect at the most recent time of use. The provisions posted on this site and contained herein supersede all previous notices or policies regarding our privacy practices and the terms and conditions that govern the use of this web site. 

#### Questions Regarding The Privacy Policy and Conditions of Use

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy and conditions of use, any concern about privacy at the CRDA or the use of this web site in general, please contact us via one of the following methods:

E-mail: info@accva.com

New Jersey Casino Reinvestment Development Authority  
Attention: Webmaster

2301 Boardwalk Hall at Mississippi Ave.

Atlantic City, NJ 08401  
(609)-449-7129
